A Guide to the Virginia Governor George F. Allen Policy Office Records, 1993-1998
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Virginia-Israel Partnership Files, 1994-1997., Extent: .425 cu. ft. (Box 4-5)
  - Dept. of Economic Development Briefing Materials, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Foundation Structure, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Itinerary, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Holocaust Curriculum Development, 1997. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Holocaust Museum Visit by Governor Allen, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Israel Aircraft Industries (Correspondence), 1997. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Israel Visit (Solitary Mission), 1996. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Other States' Activities, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Press Clippings, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Virginia-Israel Foundation, 1996. (Box 5, Folder 12)